翻譯: 奇跡道長 vince 不賣萌斯基
晚餐不錯 Annie 這話我昨晚就該說了
Great meal, Annie. I know I should've said that last night
但今晚我是發自內心的
but tonight, I really mean it.
校對: Nichole
這段你昨晚就用過了
That's what you said last night.
我以后話不能這么多了
I've gotta stop talking so much.
上次我吃得這么好
Last time I ate this well,
是我和一個小餐館的副廚約會時 Michelle
I was dating that sous chef at cookshop. Michelle.
后期: UU123
不對 等下 是叫Chelsea 沒錯
No, wait. Chelsea. Yeah.
壓制: B B
不對 她住在Chelsea
No, she lived in Chelsea!
你對她可真是情深意重啊
Sounds like that was built to last.
以后還輪的著她呢
Oh, she's still in the rotation.
這真是每個姑娘的夢想啊
That's what every girl wants,
在你的性愛機器里當一個無名齒輪
to be a nameless cog in your sex machine.
你這么說當然不行了
Oh, well, when you say it like that,
要這樣 "你愿意當我性愛機器里的齒輪嗎"
it's more like, "Will you be a cog in my sex machine?"
- 算我一份  - 洗碗機吐了
- Sign me up. - The dishwasher's throwing up.
- Leigh 你用錯皂液了 - 還有另一個嗎
- Leigh, you used the wrong soap! - Is there more than one?
哦 天啊 到處都是
Oh, god. It's everywhere!
如果是帕金森 沒啥
If that was Parkinson's, we're cool.
要是不是 干嘛呢 爸
If not, what the hell, Dad?
整頓飯你都在發短信
You've been texting the whole meal.
是Reese 我和她現在好像除了吵架就沒別的了
It's Reese, it seems like all we do is argue now
看什么電影吵 怎么用Twitter上的標簽也吵
about what movie to see, how to use hashtags on Twitter.
本來誰先掛電話還是個游戲
You know, who hangs up first used to be a game.
- 現在已經是一個嚴肅的話題了 - Ian 關于女人
- Now, it's a serious discussion. - Ian, when it comes to women,
六字箴言要牢記
there's six words you gotta remember:
你說得對 我錯了 我道歉
"You're right, I'm wrong, I'm sorry."
這只是方法之一
Ah. That's one way to go.
要是你沒錯 為什么要認錯道歉
But why would you say you're sorry if you're not sorry?
容易解決 有時 輸即是贏
It's just easier. Sometimes, you win the fight by losing it.
所以撒謊沒關系
So it's okay to lie?
有人想玩當新聞記者的游戲啊
Sounds like someone wants to be a news reporter.
不如你去我房間拿磁帶錄音機
Why don't you go in my room and get my tape recorder?
逃避問題小妙招
And that's how you dodge a question.
寶貝兒 你去哪了
Hey, sweetie. Where you been?
我以為你攝影課六點結束呢
I thought your photography class was over at six.
是啦 不過我走回家的 一路上忍不住多拍了幾張
It was, but I walked home, and I couldn't stop taking pictures.
我看到垃圾袋在微風中起舞
I saw this plastic bag just dancing on the breeze.
所以就把它弄走拍建筑去了
So I moved it out of the way and took a picture of the building,
對了 你這周末能陪我一起去紐約現代美術館
which reminds me: do you want to go to MOMA this weekend?
你想和我一起去博物館
You wanna go to a museum with me?
就我倆 同時出現嗎
Just the two of us? At the same time?
是啊 我不會讓你站在另一個房間
Well, yeah, I'm not gonna make you stand in another room and
假裝不認識我 又不是我14歲的生日聚會
pretend you don't know me. This isn't my 14th birthday party.
自從她參加了社區中心的攝影課
Eve's been a whole new person since she started
她就完全變了一個人
taking photography at the community center.
- 她愛笑了 大笑 - 一開始我們還以為她嗑藥了
- She smiles. She laughs. - At first, we thought it was drugs.
但原來她還是有情感的
But it... it turns out she can feel.
我還得給課題選幾張照片
I still have to choose photos for my class project,
但現在我選不太出來
but I'm having the hardest time narrowing it down.
也許我們能幫忙
Maybe we can help.
我不確定 你能幫得上忙
I'm not really sure this is gonna be your thing.
Eve 這是藝術 我們渾身都是藝術細胞 絕無偏見
Eve, it's art. We're arty. No judgment.
- 來吧 - 來吧 看看
- Come on. - Come on. Great.
我真的很期待看到你的人體攝影
I'm really looking forward to seeing your nudes.
- 哦 天啊 - 不錯啊
- Oh, my. - Interesting.
- 不是吧 - 男體藝術
- Holy cow. - Male nudes.
全裸 裸男 裸體 裸男
Totally naked, nude men... naked, nude men.
- 他還戴著帽子呢 - 這小伙子還挺健碩
- Oh, well, he's wearing a hat. - Yeah, there's a healthy fella.
- 他叫啥 - 我不知道
- Wha... what's his name? - I don't know.
只是班里來的模特
They're just models that came into our class.
學校給你們提供裸男
It's nice of this school to provide naked men
讓你們拍 不錯嘛
to come and expose themselves to you.
我就猜到你會操心這個
I knew you were gonna be worried about this.
我們才沒呢 我是說 沒事 Eve
We're not weird. Wha... I mean, come on, Eve.
你以為你在跟誰說話 我們挺開化的
Look who you're talking to. We are progressive people.
赤裸裸的開化
We're full-frontal progressive.
我們只是驚訝于...
We were just taken aback by... by...
- 你的天賦 - 這可真有天賦
- by your talent. - There's a lot of talent here!
- 真的 - 那可不是
- Really? - Mm-hmm.
太棒了 你們這么淡定真好
Oh, great. Thanks for being so cool, guys.
可對你們改觀了
You know, I'm impressed.
這家伙不太正常吧
That guy's not normal, right?
她這是用了特殊鏡頭吧
She's using a special lens for that?
又 見 彩 虹
第一季  第三集
電波誠譯
那個 我要扔了剩下的臘腸嗎
Okay, should I just chuck the rest of this bratwurst?
- 必須 - 好吧 這事我們得談談
- Definitely. - All right, we need to talk about this.
我們不能讓我們女兒在一個充滿裸男的
We can't have our daughter hanging out
的房間里待著 最起碼大學以前不能
in a room full of nude men, at least not until college.
或者 我還有個想法 永遠不行
Or... and this is just a thought... never!
但是參加這課后
But she's been such a
她整個人都變得樂觀開朗了啊
delight since she started taking that class.
前幾天 她夸了我公文包不錯
You know, the other day, she complimented me on my briefcase.
我立馬沖進浴室就哭了
I went into the bathroom and cried.
就好像經過這些年
It's like after all these years,
她終于覺得我們是不錯的家長了
she's finally treating us like we're the cool parents.
好吧 這事我們必須巧妙處理
All right, we have to shut this down delicately,
- 否則她就又變回老樣子了 - 那樣最糟
- or she'll go right back to being oddie. - Oddie is the worst.
告訴你 我去找她談談
I'll tell you what. I'll talk to her.
她想當藝術家 那就用藝術家的方式和她談
She wants to be an artist? I'll treat her like an artist.
- 而且你知道你脾氣 - 你什么意思 Mike
- Besides, you know how you get. - What do you mean, Mike?
你覺得我不能冷靜和她談嗎
What, you think I can't sit her down calmly
看她在...你知道嗎
and look her in the... You know what?
好吧 我已經知道會怎樣了
Okay, I am hearing that now.
Harris 等等 我有事要問你
Harris, wait! There's something I wanna ask you.
- 有點私密 - 聽著 孩子 不要信那些廣告
- It's kinda personal. - Look, man. None of those ads work.
- 原本什么水平還什么水平 - 不 真的嗎
- You've got what you got. - No, it's... Seriously?
所以 "效果保障"都是說假的咯
So "Guaranteed results" Means nothing?
但不是 剛剛你不同意我爸的觀點
But no. I saw you disagree with my Dad.
那你覺得我該拿Reese怎么辦
What do you think I should do about Reese?
我不想引火上身哦 孩子
I don't wanna get involved, man.
但是 你要知道 約會
But, you know, dating
其實不太難 就像買車
shouldn't be that hard. It's like buying a car.
選挑一輛靠譜的 用一輩子
Choose something dependable and keep it forever.
- 所以我該求婚 - 不是
- So I should propose. - No!
能試駕多少次就試駕多少次 你還小呢
Uh-uh. Test drive as many as you can. You're young.
明明有那么多車 干嘛死守著一輛破車呢
Why fix a beater when there are other cars on the lot?
聽著 就說你需要點空間 然后走開
Look, say you need some space. Then walk away.
就像這樣
It looks like this.
拜
Bye.
Luke 我是你的父親
Luke, I am your father.
此處模仿星球大戰經典橋段
- Graham 你搞什么 - 不是我的錯
- Graham, what the hell? - It's not my fault.
這要是壞了 你死定了
If this is broken, you're dead.
你應該知道 你不能在走廊里玩
You know you're not supposed to play in the hallway.
- 說得對 我錯了 我道歉 - 這樣
- You're right, I'm wrong, I'm sorry. - Well...
我想只是個小事故
I guess it was just an accident.
你能回你房間進行"帝國大反擊"嗎
Can the Empire strike back in your room?
星球大戰5
爸說的對 就好像絕地武士的心靈控制
Dad was right. It's like I learned a Jedi mind trick.
現在 你會忘記這一切
Now, you're gonna delete this.
看照片呢 你知道我喜歡藝術哪點嗎
Looking at pictures, huh? You know what I like about art?
它留給人一些想象的空間
The way it leaves certain things to the imagination.
沒錯 就是那些潛臺詞
Exactly. It's all about subtext.
有些人看到這些 看到的只是一個裸男
Some people look at this, and all they see is a naked man.
- 愚蠢 - 但是他們真正看到的是
- Idiots. - But what they're really seeing
對物化了女性的藝術范式的顛覆
is a subversion of the artistic paradigm that objectifies women.
向你脫帽致敬 那家伙頭上的帽子就算了
Well, hat's off to you, except on that guy.
但是 你知道嗎 有時 聽我說啊
Although, you know, sometimes... and hear me out on this...
用不那么激進的方式不是更顛覆嗎
wouldn't it be more subversive to do something less edgy?
- 什么方式 - 當我還小的時候 在一個
- In what way? - Well, when I was a kid, I played
車間樂隊是吉他首席 我們玩的都是重金屬
lead guitar in a garage band, and all we played was heavy metal.
你以前玩過吉他 為什么不玩了
You used to play guitar? Why did you quit?
我父母強迫的 他們想讓我吹短笛
My parents made me. They wanted me to play piccolo.
- 但是重點是 - 短笛 短笛遜爆了
- But the point is... - Piccolo? Ugh, piccolo sucks.
- 吉他超酷啊 - 我也是這么說的
- Guitar is way cooler. - That's what I said.
我是說 短笛就是小一號的長笛
I mean, piccolo is basically like a tiny flute.
我想玩正常尺寸的東西
I wanted to play real-sized things.
當然 你就該這么著
Of course you did, and you should've.
這就是為什么 你能懂真是太好了
That's why it's... it's so great that you get it.
- 我懂什么了 - 我的藝術 我
- What do I get? - My art. Me.
你知道嗎 我要用我的課題向你致敬
You know what? I'm gonna dedicate my project to you.
我就叫它"爸爸的小短笛"
I'll call it "Dad's piccolo."
別這么叫好么
Oh, don't call it that!
我剛看了篇74頁的<紅字>的論文
I just read 74 papers on a Scarlet Letter
但其中有兩頁描寫了一段場景
and all but two of them refer to a scene,
只在同名電影里出現過
that is only in the movie.
讓我猜猜 所以是兩頁的A 72頁的B咯
So let me guess. 2 "A"S and 72 "B"S.
我給那個
Well, I gave a "C" To the
叫主角Demi的女生評了C
girl who called the main character "Demi."
<紅字>電影1995年的版本女主角是黛米摩爾
- 你和Eve聊得怎么樣了 - 這個
- How'd your talk with Eve go? - Well, it was, uh... it, um...
那個
Uh... wha...
- 你干了什么好事 - 啥都沒有 真的什么都沒做
- What did you do? - I did nothing. I literally did nothing.
一分鐘前我還在讓她別太這么激進
I-I-one minute, I'm talking to her about being less edgy.
下一分鐘她就要用課題向我致敬了
And the next minute, she's dedicating the project to me.
我就知道該讓我來和她談的
I knew I should've done this!
- 你太愛他們了 - 是的 這是個大問題
- You love them too much. - I do. It's a real problem.
我爸媽肯定會這么說
You know, my parents would've just said,
我們這么說了你就這么做
"You have to stop because we said so."
我恨我爸媽老用"我們這么說了你就這么做"
I hated it when my parents used "Because I said so."
把他們丟養老院的時候我絕對也要來這句
That is exactly what I'm gonna say when I put them in a home.
我們顯然不能這么做
Well, that's clearly not an option.
我知道了 她會自覺停止
Okay, I got it. She is going to stop on her own
因為我要好好嚇唬嚇唬她
because I am going to scare her straight.
她得聽聽Carley Steiner的故事
She needs to hear the story of Carley Steiner.
誰是Carley Steiner
Who's Carley Steiner?
她是我高中的同學
She's a girl I went to high school with,
她為了個表演把頭發都剪了
and she cut off all of her hair in a performance piece.
當頭發長回來的時候 變得又粗又怪
And then when it grew back, it was all stumpy and weird.
我給這個故事加點料 來點海洛因的情節
I'm gonna jazz it up a little and throw some heroin in there.
這肯定行 肯定行
Oh, that'll work. That will work.
謝謝你這么快就趕來了
Thanks for joining me on such short notice.
你餓了么  我能湊合做碗湯
Um, are you hungry? I could scare up some soup.
我得有點男人的擔當
I had to be a man and just
簡單的告訴Reese我們完了
tell Reese in simple terms that it was over.
戀愛就像一輛車
A relationship is like a car.
即使定期保養 更換機油
And even with regular maintenance and routine oil changes,
輪胎還是有可能飛出去 然后撞向一棵樹
a tire can still fly off, and you crash into a tree.
- 好吧 - 我想說的是
- Okay. - I guess what I'm trying to say is
你不會想一輩子都只開一輛車的
that you don't want to drive the same car forever.
除非是外國車 當然你不是啦
Unless it's a foreign model, which you're not.
你是達拉斯人
You're from Dallas.
我不是在說你柵格不好...
And no one's saying you don't have a good grill...
你是要和我分手么
Are you breaking up with me?
對不起 我只是要點自己的空間
I'm sorry. I-I just... I need my own space.
理論上來說 這時候我該起身離開
Now technically, I would get up and walk away,
但是吧 這是我的房間
but you're in my room, so...
我還借你我的緊身牛仔褲
And to think I lent you my skinny jeans.
標簽 混蛋
Hashtags What a jerk.
標簽是用在主題上的 不是觀點上的
Hashtags are for topics, not opinions.
既然讓我知道了神奇六字 我啥都能干了
Now that I knew the six magic words, I could do anything.
女生們 先生們 下面由我向您呈現
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you
世界上最長的瘋狂吸管
the world's longest crazy straw.
好吧  第三次肯定能成
Okay, third time's a charm.
Graham  你瘋了嗎
Graham. Have you lost your mind?
你爸媽有一天會把這毯子給我的
Your parents are gonna give me this rug one day.
- 這不是什么大冒險 - 說的對 我錯了
- This isn't double dare. - You're right. I'm wrong.
- 對不起 - 天啊 你太可愛了
- I'm sorry. - God, you're such a cutie.
好吧 只能再玩一次哦 然后你要清理干凈
All right, one more time, and then you have to clean it up.
我來給你倒可樂
I'm gonna pour.
- 嘿Reese  - Leigh姑姑
- Hey, Reese. - Oh, hey, Aunt Leigh,
不對 你以后不是我姑姑了
except you're not my Aunt anymore.
從來都不是 一切還好吧
Never was. Is everything all right?
- Ian 剛和我分手了 - 什么 為什么
- Ian just broke up with me. - What? Why?
- 我們還玩不玩了啊  - 我不知道
- Are we gonna do this or what? - I-I don't know.
他一點都不像原來的他了
It was like I was talking to someone else.
- 他把我比作一輛舊車 - 親愛的 這太過分了
- He compared me to a used car! - Honey, that's awful.
- 國產的還是國外的 - 國產的
- Foreign or domestic? - Domestic.
真是太過分了
Honey, that's awful.
我不敢相信我的親侄會這么沒良心
I can't believe my own nephew would be so heartless.
你知道你該干什么嗎
You know what you have to do.
從中學到教訓變得堅強嗎
Learn from this and grow stronger?
不 要給他點顏色瞧瞧
No. You have to teach him a lesson.
Ian得知道他不能這么對女人
Ian has to learn that he can't treat women like this.
- 誰是他最帥的朋友 - Albino Tim
- Who is his hottest friend? - Albino Tim.
老天 這可不好辦
Oh, jeez. This is gonna be hard.
她頭后面有一整塊都禿了
So there was this entire patch in the back that was just gone,
Carlene就是在那兒注射海洛因的
and that is where Carlene would inject the heroin.
太可怕了 曾經她也是一個甜美的女孩
It was awful. I mean, one day, she was this sweet girl
有著遠大的未來 突然就這么 你在干嘛
with a bright future. And then, she was... What are you doing?
抱歉 這故事讓你變得特別生動
Oh, sorry. This story is just making you come alive.
我得捕捉下來 你繼續
I've gotta capture it. Keep going.
好吧 九十年代那時候
Uh, okay, so things got really bad
情況特別糟 海洛因重新流行起來了
in the 90s because heroin was coming back in style
- 就像帽子不再... - 往后靠一點
- just as hats were going out... - Lean back a little.
你臉上的光太足了
The light is going crazy on your face right now.
- 足是好事嗎 - 把你手臂這么擺
- Good crazy? - And put your arm up like this.
Eve我才不會 這樣么
Eve, I'm not gonna put my... Up like that?
是的
Yeah.
太棒了 媽你看上去真棒
Oh, I love it. Mom, you look great.
別管我 就當我不存在
Don't mind me. Just pretend I'm not here.
你太美了 真是塊料 現在脫掉上衣
You're beautiful. You're a natural. Now, lose the top.
等下你得見停車管理局的人
And you're meeting with the parking authority later,
所以你得把你的特斯拉從大廳開走
so you probably wanna move your Tesla from the lobby.
Kay 我這是完美犯罪 我不用付停車費
Kay, it's the perfect crime. I don't have to pay for parking,
而且停在那大家會都誤以為是抽獎用車
and it's a car that people think they can win.
Harris Harris
Harris. Harris. Oh.
我需要你給點關于Reese的建議
I need your advice about Reese.
你開玩笑的吧 這是我干正經事的地方
Oh, you gotta be kidding me, man. This is my place of business.
我照著你說的做了 我和她分手了
I did what you told me to do, and I broke up with her.
現在我滿腦子都是她
And now, I can't stop thinking about her.
- 我吃不下 睡不著  - 這才一天啊
- I can't eat. I can't sleep. - It's been one day.
關于得不到的愛情我略有心得
Well, I know a thing or two about unrequited love.
聽我說
You see, there's this
有個記者 對我來說像導師一樣
correspondent here who's like a mentor to me...
- Kay - 一路上都激勵著我
- Kay. - He just inspires me so much.
他克服了種種困難
He's overcome so many obstacles.
你在說我爸么
Are you talking about my Dad?
讓我給你介紹一下 Mike Henry的兒子
Kay, let me introduce you to Mike Henry's son.
Mike Henry 對不起 我不認識
Mike Henry? Sorry, that does not ring a bell.
你說啥 Gail 那在櫥柜里呢
What's that, Gail? Oh, it's in the cabinet.
- 好了 快點說 - 她給我發了這條短信
- All right. Make it quick. - She sent me this text message.
野餐的事多謝了 Tim
"Thanks for the picnic, Tim."
抱歉我們在太陽下躺了這么久
"Sorry we laid out in the sun so long."
這是Albino Tim從我這搶走的第三個女友
This is the third girl Albino Tim has snaked from me.
去他媽的 去他那神秘的紅色眼睛
You know, damn him and his mysterious red eyes.
- 我要 - 拜托
- I just wanna... - Oh, come on.
你這也信么
You seriously fell for this?
Reese以前給你發錯過短信嗎
Has Reese ever sent you a accidental text before today?
- 沒有  - 好了 這是假消息啦
- No. - All right, the fake text.
這是棄婦的經典手段 她沒和Tim在一起
It's a classic jilted woman move. She wasn't with Tim.
別擔心了 走吧
So just stop worrying and get out there.
你說的太對了
Wow, you're so right. God.
你知道我在哪
Oh, hey, do you know where I
能買到樓下那車的抽獎券么
can buy a raffle ticket for that car downstairs?
- 我這就有的賣 - Harris是對的
- You can buy them from me. - Harris was right.
我得把Reese放在后視鏡里
I had to put Reese in my rearview...
天啊 戀愛真太適用于車的比喻了
God, dating really lends itself to car metaphors.
總之 是時候獨自起航去往新的島嶼了
Anyway, it was time to set sail to a new island alone.
和Eve聊的怎么樣
How'd it go with Eve?
至少她沒再拍裸男照片了
Well, she's not taking pictures of naked men anymore.
我就知道  一開始就該讓你上的
I knew it. You should've gone in first.
你是終結者 你是終結者
You're the closer. You're the closer.
人們為啥總不直接派出終結者
I don't know why they don't send in closers first.
我還能說什么呢 Mike
Well, what can I say, Mike, you know?
我就走進去 撩起袖子
I just went in there. I rolled up my sleeves.
脫了衣服 天啊 Mike
I took off my shirt, and... Oh, my god, Mike.
我當時腦袋進水了 徹底進水了
I messed up. I messed up real bad.
- 你給她當模特了 - 她說我會在陰影里
- You posed for her? - She said I would be in shadow!
但是吧 那兒貌似挺亮的啊
But I don't know, man, it seemed really light in there.
媽 我把你的照片掛上去了
Mom, I just hung up your photo.
我選了那張焦點比較清晰的
I went with the ones that were a little more in focus
因為我覺得讓人們看看女人
because I think it's important for people to see
到底是什么樣的很重要
what women really look like.
慢著 人們 不止一個人
Wait, wait. People? More than one people?
這是我最棒的作品 當然得放進展覽里了
Oh, yeah. This is my best work. I've gotta put her in the show.
- 展覽  - 對啊
- Uh, eh, show? - Yeah.
明天在社區中心的藝術展
The art show at the community center tomorrow.
"爸爸的短笛"肯定大受歡迎
Dad's piccolo is going to be huge.
換個新名字 Eve 新名字
New name, Eve! New name!
你知道嗎
Ok, you know what?
這就是當開放父母的后果
This is what we get for being progressive parents.
Ian輟學了 Eve成了攝影家了
Ian is a dropout, and Eve is a pornographer now.
- 到底怎么會這樣的 Annie  - 我不知道
- What the hell happened in there, Annie? - I don't know.
那一秒鐘我就陷進去了
I just... I get caught up in the moment.
我能理解<花花公子>里面那些女人了
I understand how women end up in Playboy.
我懂了 因為一時沖動
I get it. It's a rush.
夠了 我們試過好聲好氣了
All right, we tried being cool.
現在直接告訴她不準放那張照片
We gotta just tell her flat-out that picture's gotta come down.
但是Mike 似乎有那么一瞬間
But Mike, it was like for an instant,
我終于有了個女兒 而不是什么滿腦偏見
I had a daughter and not some judgmental,
瘦不拉嘰的宿敵 我不想回糟糕Eve身邊了
skinny enemy. I don't wanna go back to garbage Eve.
糟糕Eve(前夕)
Garbage Eve, it sounds
聽起來像什么討厭的假期前夕
like the night before some horrible holiday.
好吧 我們每條路都試過了
Okay, we've exhausted every avenue.
只剩最后一個選擇了
There's only one option left to us:
去搶劫展覽
Art heist.
- 搶劫展覽  - 搶劫展覽
- Art heist? - Art heist.
好的 比你這想法還瘋狂的只有
Okay, the only thing crazier than that is...
在青少年女兒面前裸體嗎
Getting naked in front of your teenage daughter?
夠了 你是對的 好吧 就這么干
Yeah, you're right. Okay, let's do this.
你把不適用于洗碗機的肥皂放哪了
Where do you keep the wrong soap for the dishwasher?
- 不知道 水槽旁邊吧  - 謝了
- I don't know. By the sink, I think. - Thanks.
Reese要你把她的緊身牛仔褲還她
Reese wants her skinny jeans back.
我不知道放哪了
I don't know where they are.
- 你正當毛毯蓋著呢  - 這是老媽的
- You're using them as a blanket. - These are Mom's jeans.
如果真是這樣就更詭異了 給我
If that were true, it'd be even creepier. Give me those.
Ian 我知道你現在心很痛
Ian, I know you're hurting right now,
但是這大概能讓你學會對姑娘們好一點
but maybe this will teach you to be nicer to girls.
我就不該聽Harris的意見
I should've never taken Harris' advice.
啥 Harris的意見
What?! Harris' advice?
如果你表現的好 我就帶你去我的屋頂
You play your cards right, I'll take you up to my rooftop.
不過你得緊緊抱住我哦
But you're gonna have to hold onto me tight.
我有點恐高
I'm a little scared of heights.
- 他在這兒呢  - Ian
- There he is. You. - Oh, Ian.
你為啥要壞我好事
What are you doing to me, man?
就因為你他甩了他女朋友
He dumped his girlfriend because of you.
他把她跟一輛舊車相比 你知道這有多傷人嗎
He compared her to a used car. Do you know how hurtful that is?
- 你干嘛跟她講這段  - 我沒有
- Why'd you have to tell her that? - I didn't.
Leigh姑姑 這你怎么知道的
Aunt Leigh, how'd you know about that?
那可憐的小姑娘可傷心了
The poor girl was devastated.
- 你什么時候跟Reese談過了  - 我懂了
- When did you talk to Reese? - Oh, I know.
然后你姑讓她給你發了那封假短信
Right before she told her to send you that fake text.
我該猜到的 經典的棄婦招數
I should've known. Classic jilted woman move.
或許女人不會那么悲催
Maybe women wouldn't feel so jilted
如果像你這樣的男人不花心耍賤招
if guys like you would quit playing games.
- 我說的對嗎  - 別聽她的 Chelsea
- Am I right? - Don't listen to her, Chelsea.
切爾西是我住的地方
I live in Chelsea!
我...
I... Oh.
真是多謝啊 為了這妞我還假裝喜歡藜麥了
Thanks a lot. I pretended to like quinoa for that woman.
一種營養豐富全面的粗糧
Harris 你以為你有多厲害 但女人能
Harris, you think you're so smooth, but women can see
- 一眼看穿你的把戲 - 這可不是什么把戲
- right through your act. - It's not an act.
我對剛那個叫什么的女人持最崇高的敬意
I have the utmost respect for what's her name.
是叫Michelle啊
Oh, it's Michelle.
成了 看我一秒挽回
That's it. I'll fix this right now.
該死 通訊錄里有六個Michelle
Damn, six Michelles on my phone.
你覺得她算個八分還是七分
Would you say she was an eight or a seven?
- 妥妥的十分  - 所以是七分咯 謝了
- She was a ten. - So seven, thanks.
- 手機給我  - 嘿
- Give me that phone. - Hey.
- 給我...  - 別這樣搶啊
- Give me that... - Don't touch it like that.
你們倆比我還幼稚
You guys are less mature than I am.
我居然還讓你當我導師了
And to think I let you be my mentor.
才不是你讓我怎么了
Oh, you didn't let me do anything.
- 是你跑我上班地方去了  - 聯系人
- You followed me to work. - Contacts?
好了 所有的Michelle都沒了
God, no. All Michelles are done.
- 別啊  - 全刪了
- Oh. - Delete.
你就這樣...
Oh, you just... Oh.
嗨 Brenda
Hey, Brenda?
真不敢相信我們真這么干了
I cannot believe we are doing this.
親愛的 只是社區中心 又不是啥盧浮宮
Honey, it's just a community center. It's not the Louvre.
你的冒險精神哪去了
Where's your sense of adventure?
顯然全進"多功能B間"里去了
Apparently, it's in multi-purpose room B.
"多功能B間"
好了 沒有固定栓 小菜一碟
Okay, no dead bolt. This is gonna be cake.
這活你怎么學會的
How do you know how to do this?
記得我曝光的那個毛手毛腳的牙醫嗎
Remember that expose I did on a grope-y dentist?
你以為是誰偷溜進去
Who did you think broke in
藏在他供應品壁櫥里八個月啊
and hid in his supply closet for eight hours?
- 不得不靠漱口水補充水分 - 你可真壞啊
- I had to hydrate with mouthwash. - You're a badass!
不 親愛的 我只是個男人
No, honey. I'm just a man.
我照片在這兒呢
There's my photo.
你看上去年輕了二十歲
Wow, you look 20 years younger.
- 這個才是我  - 這看上去才靠譜
- That's me. - Oh, that's more like it.
我是說 這看上去才討喜
Hey, I mean that's more... like it!
好了 帶上快走
Okay, just grab it, and let's go.
親愛的 不能只拿這幅啊
Well, honey, we can't just take that one,
她會猜到是我們的 我們得多偷幾幅
she'll know it was us. We gotta steal a few others.
你認真的嗎 如果你要拿那妹子
Uh, seriously? Okay, if you get her,
- 那我要拿這個男人的  - 別這樣
- then I'm gonna take this guy. - Oh, come on.
快看 這家伙真詭異 跟著我轉悠呢
Hey, look, he's just creepy. He's following me around the room.
什么情況 我認識你
What's going on here? Hey, I know you.
對 我是Mike Henry 頻道四新聞節目的
Yeah, I'm Mike Henry, Channel 4 news.
- 聽著 我能解釋  - 不 我是說她
- Look, I can explain... - No, I meant her.
照片里那位 天哪
From the picture. Oh, my god.
我能去叫其他保安進來跟你打聲招呼嗎
Can I get the other guards in here to come say "Hi?"
他們肯定想見見你
They'd love to meet you.
我能問你個問題嗎 這家伙是不是跟著我轉悠
Can I ask you a question? Is he following us around the room?
- 不 我不覺得  - 你往那邊去點
- No, I don't... uh, no... - No, just walk that way a little bit.
- 往那邊去點  - 是 看出來了
- Walk that way a little bit. - Oh, yeah, yeah, I see it.
快跑
Run!
你們真是太難以置信了 你們說過沒啥的
I can't believe you guys! You said you were cool with it.
下一秒 背著我干這種事 太尷尬了
And then, you sneak behind my back? This is so embarrassing.
Eve 我知道你喜歡那課 但實話是
Eve, we know you love your class, but the truth is
我們不想你再拍裸體照片了
we don't want you taking nude photos anymore.
為什么不行
Why not?
- 這是個好問題  - 而我們也有了好答案
- It was a good question. - And we finally had a good answer.
- 因為我們這么說了  - 什么
- Because we said so. - What?
- 這不公平  - 對 人生就是不公平的
- That's not fair. - Yeah, well, life's not fair.
這大概持續了二十分鐘
This went on for 20 minutes.
我們說遍了教育書里的陳詞濫調
We hit every parenting cliche in the book.
所以就得這么著
And that's the way it's gonna be
只要你還生活在我們屋檐下
as long as you're living under our roof.
你們太差勁了
You guys are so lame!
- 這我能接受  - 我也是
- I can live with that. - Yeah, me too.
這是泡泡嗎
Are these bubbles?
Graham 你搞什么鬼
Whoa, Graham! What the hell's going on?
老爸 我弄了個泡泡屋
Oh, hey, Dad. I made a bubble room.
- 酷吧  - 親愛的 你不能這么做
- Pretty cool, huh? - Honey, you can't do that.
洗碗機不是玩具
The dishwasher is not a toy.
你說的對 我錯了 對不起
You're right, I'm wrong, I'm sorry.
你給我來"我錯了"這招嗎
Did you just "I'm wrong" Me?
是你爹教你的嗎
Did your Dad teach you that?
- 你知道我這招  - 我遷就你而已
- You know I did that? - I let you do that.
Graham 這招對我不管用
Graham, that doesn't work with me.
- 你被關禁閉了  - 泡泡派對結束了
- You're grounded. - Bubble party's over.
討厭 出來吧 伙計們
Oh, man. Come on, guys.
成長途中 你總覺得
Growing up, you always think
你的行事方式會不同于你父母
you'll do things differently than your parents,
你能和子女成為朋友
that you'll be friends with your kids,
平等對待他們
treat them as equals.
嗨 親愛的 親一個
Hi, sweetie. Mwah.
事實證明 說起來容易做起來難
Turns out that's easier said than done.
- Ian呢  - 在他房里呢
- Where's Ian? - He's in his bedroom.
- 他說他不餓  - 這都是我們的錯
- Said he wasn't hungry. - This is all our fault.
我們得幫他追回Reese
We have to help him get Reese back.
你說真的嗎 有完沒完了
Seriously? When does it end?
快來
Come on.
Harris 干嘛壞我好事
Oh, Harris? What are you doing to me, man?
我就知道他們命中注定在一起
I knew they were meant to be together.
我覺得大概能一周吧
I give it a week.
但事實是我們都需要界限
But the truth is we all need boundaries.
這讓我們感到安心 心心相惜 倍感關懷
They make us feel safer, connected, cared for.
再說如果沒有了 那咱還反對個啥
And without 'em, we'd have nothing to rebel against.
- 不錯吧  - 不錯
- Not bad, huh? - No, not bad.
你知道 搖滾明星通常都跟模特約會的
And you know, rock stars always do date models.
你介意我把我那張照片掛櫥子上嗎
Would you mind if I hung my photo up in our closet?
你介意我放專輯封面上嗎
Would you mind if I use it for my album cover?
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組